Guide to the Central Washington University Relations, Subject Files 1960-2005 (bulk 1980-2000)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Relations, Subject Files
1960-2005 (bulk 1980-2000)
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG027-06-33
Central Washington University Relations
17.0 cubic feet 31 letter sized document cases and 3 legal sized document boxes Press releases, newspaper clippings, reports, correspondence, and photographic prints in good condition
This collection consists of subject files retained by the University Relations and Development Office at Central Washington University from the 1960s to 2005.
Historical Note
Central Washington University's Advancement Office began as the Office of Public Service in 1938. In 1946 the office was renamed the Publications Office, a name which it retained until 1962 when it became part of the Office of Auxiliary Services. After 1966 it became the College Relations and Financial Aid Office and later, in 1969, the College Information Office. When Central Washington State College became a university in 1977, the office was renamed the University Information Office. In 1979 it was called the University Relations Office, and in 1993 it became the University Advancement Office.
The bulk of this collection covers the time period from 1980 to 2000 and contains news releases, newspaper clippings, reports, correspondence and some photographic prints produced or collected by the University Relations and Development Office of Central Washington University. Files of interest include biographies of building namesakes, significant events on campus and department, program and office activities and histories.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Alphabetical by title of subject or topic heading
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University Relations
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Universities and colleges--Washington (State)
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
Photographic prints
- Academic Achievement Programs (Box-folder 1-1)
- Academic Affairs (Box-folder 1-2)
- Academic Services (Box-folder 1-3)
- Accounting (Box-folder 1-4)
- Accreditation (Box-folder 1-5)
- ADA – Accessibility Survey Report, 1998 (Box-folder 1-6)
- ADA Affairs – Special Report, 1997 (Box-folder 1-7)
- ADA Affairs and Student Assistance (Box-folder 1-8)
- ADA Affairs and Student Assistance – Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1-9)
- Administrative Management and Business Education (Box-folder 1-10)
- Administrative Organization, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1-11)
- Administrative Salary Ranges (Box-folder 1-12)
- Admissions – Minority Recruitment (Box-folder 1-13)
- Admissions and Academic Advising Services (Box-folder 1-14)
- Admissions Tax (Ellensburg) (Box-folder 1-15)
- Affirmative Action Office (Box-folder 1-16)
- Affirmative Action Plan, 1998 (Box-folder 1-17)
- Aerospace Studies (Box-folder 2-1)
- Alternative School (Box-folder 2-2)
- Alumni and Development (Box-folder 2-3)
- Alumni Board Members (Box-folder 2-4)
- Alumni Relations Office (Box-folder 2-5)
- American Marketing Association – Student Chapter (Box-folder 2-6)
- Appointing Authority (Box-folder 2-7)
- Archives (State Regional) and Records Management (Box-folder 2-8)
- Asia University America Program (Box-folder 2-9)
- Asia Pacific Studies (Box-folder 2-10)
- Anthropology – News Releases (Box-folder 2-11)
- Anthropology – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 2-12)
- Art Department – Degree in Graphic Design and Studio Art (Box-folder 2-13)
- Art Department – News Releases (Box-folder 2-14)
- Art Department – Newspaper clippings (Box-folder 2-15)
- Associated Student of CWU – Constitution (Box-folder 2-16)
- Associated Student of CWU – Entertainment (Box-folder 2-17)
- Associated Student of CWU – General File (Box-folder 2-18)
- Associated Student of CWU – News Releases (Box-folder 2-19)
- Athletic Department (Box-folder 3-1)
- Athletic Department – Title IX Compliance (Box-folder 3-2)
- Audit Reports – Associated Students Funds (Box-folder 3-3)
- Audit Reports – General (Box-folder 3-4)
- Audit Reports – Housing and Food Services (Box-folder 3-5)
- Auxiliary Services (Box-folder 3-6)
- Biological Sciences – News Releases (Box-folder 3-7)
- Biological Sciences – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 3-8)
- Biological Sciences – Yakima Basin Center (Box-folder 3-9)
- Bluelight / Safety Escort Services (Box-folder 3-10)
- Boys / Girls State (Box-folder 3-11)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1986 (Box-folder 3-12)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1987 (Box-folder 3-13)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1988 (Box-folder 3-14)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1989 (Box-folder 3-15)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1990 (Box-folder 4-1)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1991 (Box-folder 4-2)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1992 (Box-folder 4-3)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1993 (Box-folder 4-4)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1994 (Box-folder 4-5)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1995 (Box-folder 4-6)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1996 (Box-folder 4-7)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1997 (Box-folder 4-8)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1997 (Box-folder 4-9)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1998 (Box-folder 4-10)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 1999 (Box-folder 5-1)
- Budget Reports – Capital, 2000 (Box-folder 5-2)
- Budget Reports – News Releases (Box-folder 5-3)
- Budget Reports – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 5-4)
- Budget Reports – Operational, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 5-5)
- Budget Reports – Operational, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5-6)
- Budget Reports – Operational, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5-7)
- Buildings – Alford-Montgomery Hall (Box-folder 5-8)
- Buildings – Architects (Box-folder 5-9)
- Buildings – Bakke Machine Room (Box-folder 5-10)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Equipment Request (Box-folder 5-11)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – History (Box-folder 5-12)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Renovation (Box-folder 5-13)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Renovation – News Releases and Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 5-14)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Renovation Building Program (Box-folder 6-1)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Renovation Committee (Box-folder 6-2)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6-3)
- Buildings – Barge Hall – Showcase (Box-folder 6-4)
- Buildings – Barracks (Old Dorms) (Box-folder 6-5)
- Buildings – Barto Hall (Box-folder 6-6)
- Buildings – Beck Hall (Box-folder 6-7)
- Buildings – Black Hall (Box-folder 6-8)
- Buildings – Black Hall – Remodel and Addition (Box-folder 6-9)
- Buildings – Bouillon Hall (Box-folder 6-10)
- Buildings – Bouillon Hall – Remodel (Box-folder 6-11)
- Buildings – CHCI (Box-folder 6-12)
- Buildings – Carmody-Munroe Hall (Box-folder 6-13)
- Buildings – Carmody-Munro Hall – Douglas A. Munro (Box-folder 6-14)
- Buildings – Construction Projects (Box-folder 6-15)
- Buildings – Courson Conference Center (Box-folder 6-16)
- Buildings – Courson Hall (Box-folder 6-17)
- Buildings – Davies Hall (Box-folder 6-18)
- Buildings – Dean Hall (Box-folder 6-19)
- Buildings – Edison Hall (Box-folder 6-20)
- Buildings – Elwood Manor (Box-folder 6-21)
- Buildings – Farrell Hall (Box-folder 6-22)
- Buildings – General File – News Releases (Box-folder 7-1)
- Buildings – General File – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 7-2)
- Buildings – General History (Box-folder 7-3)
- Buildings – Getz-Short Apartments (Box-folder 7-4)
- Buildings – Green Hall (Box-folder 7-5)
- Buildings – Grupe Conference Center (Box-folder 7-6)
- Buildings – Hebeler Hall (Box-folder 7-7)
- Buildings – Hertz Hall (Box-folder 7-8)
- Buildings – Hertz Hall – Wayne S. Hertz – News Releases (Box-folder 7-9)
- Buildings – Hertz Hall – Wayne S. Hertz – Photographs and Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 7-10)
- Buildings – Hitchcock Hall (Box-folder 7-11)
- Buildings – Hogue Hall (Box-folder 7-12)
- Buildings – Holmes Dining Hall (Box-folder 7-13)
- Buildings – Jungeward Building (Box-folder 7-14)
- Buildings – Kennedy Hall (Box-folder 7-15)
- Buildings – Kohler Instruction Room (Room 106 Hebeler Hall) (Box-folder 7-16)
- Buildings – Kamola Hall (Box-folder 7-17)
- Buildings – Landscaping – Urban Renewal (Box-folder 7-18)
- Buildings – Language and Literature Building (Box-folder 7-19)
- Buildings – Lind Hall (Box-folder 7-20)
- Buildings – Lind Hall – Edmund L. Lind (Box-folder 7-21)
- Buildings – Sue Lombard Hall (Box-folder 7-22)
- Buildings – Mayberry Arboretum (Box-folder 7-23)
- Buildings – McConnell Auditorium (Box-folder 7-24)
- Buildings – McConnell Hall (Box-folder 7-25)
- Buildings – Meisner Hall (Box-folder 8-1)
- Buildings – Michaelsen-Randall Hall (Box-folder 8-2)
- Buildings – Michaelsen-Randall Hall – Helen Michaelsen (Box-folder 8-3)
- Buildings – Michaelsen-Randall Hall – Reino W. Randall (Box-folder 8-4)
- Buildings – Mitchell Hall (Box-folder 8-5)
- Buildings – Mitchell Hall – Perry Mitchell (Box-folder 8-6)
- Buildings – Moore Hall (Box-folder 8-7)
- Buildings – Mount Room (Room 290 Brooks Library) (Box-folder 8-8)
- Buildings – Munson Hall (Box-folder 8-9)
- Buildings – Muzzall Hall (Box-folder 8-10)
- Buildings – Name proposals (Box-folder 8-11)
- Buildings – Names for Buildings and Rooms (Box-folder 8-12)
- Buildings – Naming Policy (Box-folder 8-13)
- Buildings – Nicholson Pavilion (Box-folder 8-14)
- Buildings – Nicholson Pavilion – Leo S. Nicholson (Box-folder 8-15)
- Buildings – North Hall (Box-folder 8-16)
- Buildings – Peterson Hall (Box-folder 8-17)
- Buildings – Physical Education Building (Box-folder 8-18)
- Buildings – Physical Plant Facilities (Box-folder 8-19)
- Buildings – Projections, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 8-20)
- Buildings – Projections, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 8-21)
- Buildings – Psychology Building (Box-folder 9-1)
- Buildings – Quigley Hall (Box-folder 9-2)
- Buildings – Samuelson Union Building (Box-folder 9-3)
- Buildings – Samuelson Union Building – E. E. Samuelson (Box-folder 9-4)
- Buildings – Science Building (Box-folder 9-5)
- Buildings – Shaw-Smyser Hall (Box-folder 9-6)
- Buildings – Shaw-Smyser Hall – Reginald Shaw (Box-folder 9-7)
- Buildings – Shaw-Smyser Hall – Selden F. Smyser (Box-folder 9-8)
- Buildings – Short Apartments (Box-folder 9-9)
- Buildings – Sogge Woodworking Room (Box-folder 9-10)
- Buildings – Sparks Hall (Box-folder 9-11)
- Buildings – Spurgeon Gallery (Box-folder 9-12)
- Buildings – Stephens-Whitney Hall – William F. Stephens (Box-folder 9-13)
- Buildings – Stephens-Whitney Hall – Henry J. Whitney (Box-folder 9-14)
- Buildings – Student Health Center (Box-folder 9-15)
- Buildings – Tomlinson Athletic Field (Box-folder 9-16)
- Buildings – Tunstall Dining Hall (Box-folder 9-17)
- Buildings – University of Washington Manashtash Ridge Astronomy Observatory (Box-folder 9-18)
- Buildings – Wahle Apartments (Box-folder 9-19)
- Buildings – Wilson Hall (Box-folder 9-20)
- Buildings – Wright Instructional Media Center (Box-folder 9-21)
- Buildings and Grounds – Board of Trustees Motions and Actions (Box-folder 9-22)
- Buildings and Grounds – Board of Trustees Motions and Actions, 1986 (Box-folder 10-1)
- Business Administration – News Releases (Box-folder 10-2)
- Business Administration – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 10-3)
- Business and Economics – General File (Box-folder 10-4)
- Business and Economics – News Releases (Box-folder 10-5)
- Business and Economics – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 10-6)
- Business and Financial Affairs – General File (Box-folder 10-7)
- Business and Financial Affairs – News Releases (Box-folder 10-8)
- Business and Financial Affairs – Newspaper clippings (Box-folder 10-9)
- Business Services and Contracts (Box-folder 10-10)
- Business Week – News Releases (Box-folder 10-11)
- Business Week – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 10-12)
- Campus Climate Task Force (Box-folder 11-1)
- Campus Compact (Box-folder 11-2)
- Campus Disturbance (Box-folder 11-3)
- Campus Events, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 11-4)
- Campus Facility Master Plan (Box-folder 11-5)
- Campus Life – News Releases (Box-folder 11-6)
- Campus Life – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 11-7)
- Campus Police – News Releases (Box-folder 11-8)
- Campus Police – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 11-9)
- Campus Security – General File (Box-folder 11-10)
- Career Development – General File (Box-folder 11-11)
- Career Development – News Releases (Box-folder 11-12)
- Career Development – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 11-13)
- Central Association for Lifelong Learning (Box-folder 11-14)
- Central Investment Fund – News Releases (Box-folder 11-15)
- Central Investment Fund – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 11-16)
- Central Cares (Box-folder 12-1)
- Central Safety Center (Box-folder 12-2)
- Central Washington Archaeological Society (Box-folder 12-3)
- Cheerleaders (Box-folder 12-4)
- Chemistry – News Releases (Box-folder 12-5)
- Chemistry – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 12-6)
- Chimpanzee and Human Communication Institute – General File (Box-folder 12-7)
- Chimpanzee and Human Communication Institute – News Releases (Box-folder 12-8)
- Chimpanzee and Human Communication Institute – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 12-9)
- Civil Service Staff – News Releases (Box-folder 12-10)
- Classic Film Series – News Releases (Box-folder 12-11)
- Classic Film Series – Newspaper clippings (Box-folder 12-12)
- Classified Staff Retirees (Box-folder 12-13)
- Clubs (Box-folder 12-14)
- Collective Bargaining (Box-folder 12-15)
- College of Arts and Humanities (Box-folder 13-1)
- College of Education and Professional Studies (Box-folder 13-2)
- College of the Sciences (Box-folder 13-3)
- Commencement (Box-folder 13-4)
- Commercial Activities (Box-folder 13-5)
- Communication Services (Box-folder 13-6)
- Communications Department – News Releases (Box-folder 13-7)
- Communications Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 13-8)
- Computer Sciences Department (Box-folder 13-9)
- Conferences and Workshops – News Releases (Box-folder 13-10)
- Conferences and Workshops – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 13-11)
- Continuing Education – News Releases (Box-folder 13-12)
- Continuing Education – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 13-13)
- Cooperative Education and Internships (Box-folder 14-1)
- Curriculum and Supervision (Box-folder 14-2)
- CWU Centennial (Box-folder 14-3)
- CWU Partnership Schools – Ellensburg (Box-folder 14-4)
- Dean’s Scholars (Box-folder 14-5)
- Desert Shield (Box-folder 14-6)
- Dining Services (Box-folder 14-7)
- Dining Services – National Association of College and University Food Service (Box-folder 14-8)
- Douglas Honors College (Box-folder 14-9)
- Drug Abuse Prevention Program (Box-folder 14-10)
- Earthquake – Campus (Box-folder 14-11)
- Economic Development and Public Policy (Box-folder 14-12)
- Economic Impact Statement (Box-folder 14-13)
- Economics Department (Box-folder 14-14)
- Education Week (Box-folder 14-15)
- Educational Opportunities Program, 1969 (Box-folder 14-16)
- Educational Opportunities Program, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 14-17)
- Educational Opportunities Program – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 14-18)
- Elderhostel (Box-folder 15-1)
- Employee Council (Box-folder 15-2)
- Employee of the Month (Box-folder 15-3)
- Energy Services Project (Box-folder 15-4)
- English Department – News Releases (Box-folder 15-5)
- English Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 15-6)
- Enrollment – News Releases (Box-folder 15-7)
- Enrollment – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 15-8)
- Enrollment Management and Marketing (Box-folder 15-9)
- Entertainers (Box-folder 15-10)
- Entertainment (Box-folder 15-11)
- Environmental Studies (Box-folder 15-12)
- Ethnic Studies Program (Box-folder 15-13)
- Exchange / Visiting Faculty – General (Box-folder 15-14)
- Exchange / Visiting Faculty – News Releases and Photographs (Box-folder 15-15)
- Exempt Administrative and Professional Staff (Box-folder 15-16)
- Extended University Programs – General File (Box-folder 15-17)
- Extended University Programs – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 15-18)
- Extended University Programs – Lynnwood Center – News Releases (Box-folder 16-1)
- Extended University Programs – Lynnwood Center – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 16-2)
- Extended University Programs – Moses Lake Center (Box-folder 16-3)
- Extended University Programs – SeaTac Center – News Releases (Box-folder 16-4)
- Extended University Programs – SeaTac Center – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 16-5)
- Extended University Programs – Steilacoom Center (Box-folder 16-6)
- Extended University Programs – Wenatchee Center (Box-folder 16-7)
- Extended University Programs – Yakima Center – News Releases (Box-folder 16-8)
- Extended University Programs – Yakima Center – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 16-9)
- Facilities Management (Box-folder 16-10)
- Faculty – General File (Box-folder 16-11)
- Faculty – News Releases (Box-folder 16-12)
- Faculty – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 16-13)
- Faculty Leave (Box-folder 16-14)
- Faculty Reappointment (Box-folder 16-15)
- Faculty Salary Adjustments (Box-folder 17-1)
- Faculty Senate – General File (Box-folder 17-2)
- Faculty Senate – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 17-3)
- Family Consumer Sciences – New Releases (Box-folder 17-4)
- Family Consumer Sciences – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 17-5)
- Financial Aid – General File (Box-folder 17-6)
- Financial Aid – News Releases (Box-folder 17-7)
- Financial Aid – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 17-8)
- Flag Pavilion (Box-folder 17-9)
- Flight Technology Program (Box-folder 17-10)
- Foreign Language – News Releases (Box-folder 17-11)
- Foreign Language – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 17-12)
- Foundation (CWU) – General File (Box-folder 18-1)
- Foundation (CWU) – News Releases (Box-folder 18-2)
- Foundation (CWU) – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 18-3)
- Fund Drives (Box-folder 18-4)
- Geography and – News Releases (Box-folder 18-5)
- Geography and – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 18-6)
- Geology – News Releases (Box-folder 18-7)
- Geology – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 18-8)
- Graduate Studies and Research – General File (Box-folder 18-9)
- Graduate Studies and Research – News Releases (Box-folder 18-10)
- Graduate Studies and Research – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 18-11)
- Grants (Box-folder 18-12)
- Hearings (Box-folder 18-13)
- Higher Education Coordinating Board – News Releases (Box-folder 18-14)
- Higher Education Coordinating Board – Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 18-15)
- Graphic Design (Box-folder 18-16)
- History of Central – 75th Anniversary (Box-folder 19-1)
- History of Central – General File (Box-folder 19-2)
- History of Central – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 19-3)
- History Department (Box-folder 19-4)
- Homecoming (Box-folder 19-5)
- Housing (Box-folder 19-6)
- Humanities Program (Box-folder 19-7)
- Industrial and Engineering Technology (Box-folder 19-8)
- Information File (Box-folder 19-9)
- Information Resources (Box-folder 19-10)
- Institute for Science and Society (Box-folder 19-11)
- Institutional Research (Box-folder 19-12)
- International Studies and Programs –News Releases (Box-folder 19-13)
- International Studies and Programs – News Releases (Box-folder 20-1)
- International Studies and Programs – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 20-2)
- Japanese Gardens (Box-folder 20-3)
- KCAT Radio – General File (Box-folder 20-4)
- KCAT Radio – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 20-5)
- KCWU Television (Box-folder 20-6)
- Latin American Affairs (Box-folder 20-7)
- Laughing Horse Summer Theater (Box-folder 20-8)
- Law and Justice – News Releases (Box-folder 20-9)
- Law and Justice – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 20-10)
- Lawsuits – News Releases, etc. (Box-folder 20-11)
- Lawsuits – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 20-12)
- Lectures – News Releases (Box-folder 20-13)
- Lecturers – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 20-14)
- Legislative News – News Releases (Box-folder 20-15)
- Legislative News – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 20-16)
- Library – News Releases (Box-folder 21-1)
- Library – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 21-2)
- Lobbying Activities and Expenditures (Box-folder 21-3)
- Loss Control Management (Box-folder 21-4)
- Mapping your education (Box-folder 21-5)
- Master Plan (Box-folder 21-6)
- Mathematics Department (Box-folder 21-7)
- McNair Scholarship Program (Box-folder 21-8)
- Medical Technology (Box-folder 21-9)
- Mexico City Program (Box-folder 21-10)
- Migrant and Indian Center (Box-folder 21-11)
- Military Sciences – News Releases (Box-folder 21-12)
- Military Sciences – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 21-13)
- Minority Coalition (Box-folder 21-14)
- Minority Retention (Box-folder 21-15)
- Miscellaneous (Box-folder 21-16)
- Music Department – General File (Box-folder 21-17)
- Music Department – New Building (Box-folder 21-18)
- Music Department – News Releases (Box-folder 22-1)
- Music Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 22-2)
- Music Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 22-3)
- Music Bands (Box-folder 22-4)
- Music Choral (Box-folder 22-5)
- Music Jazz – News Releases (Box-folder 22-6)
- Music Jazz – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 22-7)
- Music Orchestra (Box-folder 22-8)
- Music Preparatory Program (Box-folder 22-9)
- Music Recitals – News Releases (Box-folder 22-10)
- Music Recitals – News Releases (Box-folder 23-1)
- Music Recitals – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 23-2)
- Music Recitals – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 23-3)
- Native American Council (Box-folder 23-4)
- Non-Academic Services (Box-folder 23-5)
- Observer (Box-folder 23-6)
- Open House (Box-folder 23-7)
- Organizational Structuring (Box-folder 23-8)
- Paramedic Program (Box-folder 23-9)
- Parents Weekend (Box-folder 23-10)
- Parking Proposal (Box-folder 23-11)
- Phi Kappa Phi (Honor Society) (Box-folder 23-12)
- Philosophy (Box-folder 23-13)
- Physical Education – General File (Box-folder 23-14)
- Physical Education – News Releases (Box-folder 23-15)
- Physical Education – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 24-1)
- Physics Department (Box-folder 24-2)
- Policy Statement (Box-folder 24-3)
- Political Science (Box-folder 24-4)
- Power Pole Issue (Box-folder 24-5)
- Presidential Candidates (Box-folder 24-6)
- Presidential Search Committee (Box-folder 24-7)
- President’s Associates (Box-folder 24-8)
- President’s Office (Box-folder 24-9)
- President’s Scholar Award (Box-folder 24-10)
- Preview Week (Box-folder 24-11)
- Primate Behavior and Ecology (Box-folder 24-12)
- Provost’s Office – General File (Box-folder 24-13)
- Provost’s Office – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 24-14)
- Psychology – News Releases (Box-folder 25-1)
- Psychology – Newspaper Clipiings (Box-folder 25-2)
- Registrar’s Office (Box-folder 25-3)
- Religious Studies (Box-folder 25-4)
- Residence Hall (Box-folder 25-5)
- Residential Services – General File (Box-folder 25-6)
- Residential Services – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 25-7)
- Resource Management (Box-folder 25-8)
- Retirement Association – General File (Box-folder 25-9)
- Retirement Association – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 25-10)
- Retirement Plans (Box-folder 25-11)
- Retired Senior Volunteer Program (Box-folder 25-12)
- Running Start Program (Box-folder 25-13)
- Sarah Spurgeon Gallery (Box-folder 26-1)
- Science Building (Box-folder 26-2)
- Science Education (Box-folder 26-3)
- Sculptures On Campus (Box-folder 26-4)
- Senior / Youth Ventures (Box-folder 26-5)
- Sister Universities (Box-folder 26-6)
- Sociology Department – New Releases (Box-folder 26-7)